♪
[UKA]
I may as well have not existed.
Back then,
I felt nothing...
and thought nothing.
I want to change.
Each time,
my wishes died
without coming true.
No one felt anything
when I was around.
Or if they did, it was pity.
It hurts.
I feel awful.
Is this how life is?
What could change it?
[gasps]
♪
Honey lemon soda.
What I've been looking for?
It was you.
♪
Uh!
Oh.
You're up.
[UKA]
He's here.
My mind is fuzzy.
Am I dreaming?
I must be...
just like before.
Miura?
[whimpering]
I love you.
Hm?
[UKA]
If I'm dreaming,
I can say anything.
I want to be yours.
Make me your girlfriend.
[UKA]
Yeah.
Just a dream.
How else could this happen?
Could I ever be so lucky?
SPARKLE 12 HONEY LEMON SODA
[FEMALE STUDENT 1]
Morning!
[FEMALE STUDENT 2]
Hey, there.
[UKA] Was all that
a dream, yesterday?
[whimpering]
[FEMALE STUDENT 3]
Hey, hey!
[indistinct chatter]
Hm!
[ALL]
Hmm?
[UKA]
No, it wasn't.
It was real!
So...
-I said I love him.
-[AYUMI] Uka.
-[UKA] I said I love him.
[AYUMI] Uka!
[UKA]
I said I love him!
And that wasn't all.
It gets worse!
I want to be yours.
Make me your girlfriend.
-I said the quiet part
out loud... -[AYUMI] Hello.
-Earth to Uka?
-...straight to his face!
And if that wasn't bad enough,
I passed out right after.
-[AYUMI] Whoa!
-[Uka gasps]
-[UKA] How could I dream
about that? -Hello?
I wonder.
Did I scare him?
-[indistinct chatter]
-I must have!
'Sup, besties?!
-[AYUMI] Uh, Kai?
-[SATORU] Hm?
[UKA] Are things gonna
go back to normal?
Miura.
I love you.
Uh...
Hmm.
-[UKA] So...
-Hm.
Kai.
What'd you do?
[UKA]
What now?
I can't go back to "normal."
[indistinct chatter]
[leaves rustling]
What?!
You said that?
Like, to him?
What have you done with Uka?
[shuddering]
[UKA] I couldn't keep
it from Ayumi any longer.
[AYUMI] [excited laughter]
Amazing!
Go on!
And?
Hm? Hm?
More!
[chuckles excitedly]
-More?
-[AYUMI] His reply!
Uh, "reply?"
Mm-hmm.
Tell me!
Not exactly sure.
I was just happy
that I told him.
Beyond that, I don't know.
[Ayumi chuckles awkwardly]
[AYUMI]
That's so you.
[UKA]
I guess...
typically,
the other person replies?
-[AYUMI] All good, then.
-[Uka gasps]
But still...I'm sure Kai has
something he wants to say, too.
Now is the time.
Yeah?
Take the step.
[UKA]
Yeah.
[UKA] Thank you.
You're right!
Next, I'll talk to him.
I'll accept any answer!
It'll be fine.
This is nothing.
Just another step.
[indistinct chatter]
3 STEPS FORWARD
2 STEPS BACK
Whoa,
you guys need to see this!
Over here!
-Huh?
[UKA]
Flowers?
[SHIRAISHI] Remember?
Those third years
who locked Kai
in the storage room?
Just now, the one with
the two-toned hair
left that for you!
-[AYUMI] But why?
-[Tonbo laughs]
[TONBO] Flowers?
Someone messing with you?
-[AYUMI] Shut it, Tonbo.
-[whimpering]
[SHIRAISHI] He's got a point.
That might be it.
[AYUMI]
Well, maybe.
But that doesn't
make any sense!
Uh.
Shut it.
You're not scared?
If you don't watch it,
you might get hurt, girl.
[SHIRAISHI]
Wait, he left a note!
Hold on.
If it says anything mean...
Death!
Prison!
UKA ISHIMORI, I LOVE YOU.
NAOKI FROM 3-D
-[all gasp, scream]
-[SHIRAISHI] What is this?
[YURU] He wrote
a freakin' love letter?
-Oh, my God!
-[SHIRAISHI] Ishimori,
what'd you say to him?
-[UKA] I don't know!
-[AYUMI] You won him over!
[UKA]
By accident!
[TONBO] Kai!
Ishimori got a love letter
from a third-year!
[SATORU]
Wait, for real?
[TOMOYA]
Huh?
Why not go out with him?
Not every day you get
a confession from a third-year,
and it's probably the last one
-you'll see for a while!
-[SHIRAISHI] Say what?
[AYUMI]
I hate you so much, Tonbo.
Hey.
Why not see if you like him?
-What's the worst...
-[KAI] Bad idea.
-...that could happen?
-She's not ready for that.
All right?
[breathes shakily]
[KAI]
Just think it over carefully.
[AYUMI] Hold up.
What's your deal, Kai?
You totally missed the point.
She's not gonna date him!
[UKA]
I'm not ready yet,
huh?
[indistinct chatter]
[YASUSHI]
Oh, come on.
-Did Kai need more fangirls?
-Gets a lotta love
for being a cheer squad boy.
Yeah, lucky.
Hey, why don't we make
a fan club for us?
[FEMALE STUDENT 4]
...fun together.
[FEMALE STUDENT 5]
It's our treat.
[YASUSHI] Never mind.
Whatever.
[UKA]
Even the older girls like him.
[FEMALE STUDENT 4]
Gotta look cute!
[UKA]
Miura's words have weight.
They always mean something.
So...
♪
Just think it over carefully.
[UKA] What could he have meant
when he said that?
I finally feel comfortable
around him.
But I'm not ready to date him?
What exactly are we?
If I try to think back,
I'm still where I started.
So was I wrong?
Should I not have told him
how I felt?
♪
[footsteps receding]
What do I do?
I told him
I wanted to be his girlfriend.
[whimpering]
I messed up.
[SERINA]
Uka?
[whimpering]
[gasps]
[SERINA]
What happened with Kai?
Nothing.
[SERINA]
Let me go talk to him.
Uh.
[UKA] [gasps]
Wait! Please don't!
-But look at you.
-[UKA] It's okay.
I can't burden him
any more than I have.
Huh?
I've done enough.
I can't make him carry more.
My love is too heavy.
[UKA]
No.
I'm falling back on old habits.
♪
Well, I don't think he wants me
to tell you about this.
But...
the other day?
After they closed
the storage room?
♪
[keys jingling]
-[KAI] Hey.
-Uh?
[SERINA]
That the key to the roof?
[KAI]
Got lucky.
I guess it's all mine, now.
Oh, yeah?
Just like that?
Then I assume that's gonna be
your new spot to take naps?
You sure love your alone time.
Not quite.
You're close,
but I'll invite Ishimori.
Huh?
[SERINA] You're scared
you're burdening him,
but would Kai say that
if he felt that way?
You should pay attention.
How's he acted all this time?
[KAI]
Go find someone.
Ask for help.
You try to mess with her again,
you'll be answering to me.
Do you realize
how silly your dreams are?
They're small.
I'll make them all come true.
Whenever things go wrong,
tell me.
I'm with you.
Always.
Ishimori.
C'mere.
[whimpering]
Whoa.
Uh...
[UKA]
I know what he'll say.
-Still.
-Ah...
-[UKA] I'm scared to hear him
actually say it. -Huh.
It won't be easy,
and it might hurt,
but...
[UKA]
Miura?
Hah.
I don't like
how this morning went.
If you have the time right now,
I'll be in the classroom.
Meet me there!
[FEMALE STUDENT 6] Huh?
Who's she?
[UKA]
I want you to hear my feelings.
Give me the chance...
one more time!
[UKA]
Let me be able to say it...
and say it clearly!
♪
It's okay.
This won't be an ending.
♪
[door slides open]
[footsteps approaches]
♪
[door slides shut]
-Thank you--
-[KAI] Can I go first?
Hmm.
Okay.
Did ya think carefully?
I have questions,
so answer honestly.
How do you feel now?
Got your head all sorted out?
Do you regret what you said?
Or are you ready to hear
how I feel,
Ishimori?
♪
Because I'm in love
with you, too.
[gasps]
♪
[sighs]
[Uka whimpering]
[Uka crying]
[KAI] [sighs]
You're such a pain.
Come on.
If you can't talk,
at least look at me.
[whimpering]
[sobbing silently]
♪
[Kai exhales]
Hey.
It's fine.
The past eight months,
I've been slowly
falling in love.
♪
I'm serious about this.
Okay?
Uh...
[breathes shakily]
[UKA]
I'm losing control.
The words are coming.
I can't hold them back!
I'm in love with you!
I love you so much!
[Uka sobs]
I know.
[UKA]
Really, I love you.
[Uka sniffles]
[KAI]
Yeah, I got it.
You told me.
[Uka gasps]
[whimpering]
[UKA]
I fell for someone.
I'm in love.
I'm not afraid.
Not anymore!
Now,
I'll follow you anywhere.
[birds chirping]
[signal beeps]
♪
[UKA]
I finally told him how I felt.
My heart's so full,
I'm worried it'll burst.
[MIRU]
Kai! Mornin'!
Meetin' someone?
I'm trying to.
[MIRU]
Oh.
[UKA]
Good morning, Miura!
Who are you waiting for
on this beautiful day?
You're really gonna
make me say it's you?
♪
Uh.
[KAI]
Your hair smells nice.
Did you just wash it?
[shudders]
[breathes shakily]
-Uh!
-[gasps]
Uh.
[Uka breathes shakily]
[Kai sighs]
[UKA]
I never imagined
the future would
look so bright.
[breathes shakily]
[KAI]
Sorry.
[UKA] No.
It's fine!
[Shiraishi cheering]
They're holding hands!
Seems like you two are getting
chummier by the day!
More than that. It looks like
you guys are in love!
Careful!
Yeah, we are.
[all gasp]
Nice!
[ALL]
What?!
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
He just said it!
What happened to our cute,
innocent Ishimori?
When did this start?
How long have you two been
going out behind our backs,
anyway?
You're gonna
shake her head right off!
I don't think we're going out!
He said you're in love,
didn't he?
How the heck
are you not going out yet?
Well, no one said
anything about dating.
People can go out
without making it official.
[ALL]
Huh?
[Uka gasps]
But don't you wanna
make it official
and actually be his girlfriend?
More than anything!
Yeah, of course.
But I figured...
there were still some steps
before that?
I mean, like,
what is dating, actually?
[SHIRAISHI] Kai's the worst
first love she could have.
[YURU]
That's rough.
I'm sure it'll be okay!
The constant panic
is part of my girl's charm!
♪
[UKA]
So, Miura.
What are we...
and what's next?
[YASUSHI] So, uh...
I heard that you and Ishimori
aren't actually going out?
Or that's what I hear
she's telling people, lately.
But what do you think?
Figures.
Ishimori.
Hmm.
[UKA] Uh.
Yes?
[UKA] I'm calm.
So calm.
Hey, Kai?
Why do you still call her
"Ishimori?"
-That's kinda weird for you.
-Huh?
[TONBO] You usually
jump straight to first names,
even with people you just met.
-Yeah, good point.
-[AYUMI] Huh?
You're still acting
formal with her,
after all this time.
Any reason?
Uh...
[Tonbo laughs]
[TONBO] Do you not know
her first name?
-Uka.
-[Uka gasps]
Was that okay?
Did I say it right?
♪
[YASUSHI] Uh-oh. Someone check
if she's breathing.
[TONBO] But all he did
was just say your name.
[school bell chimes]
Well.
Off to the assembly.
See you.
[breathes shakily]
[YASUSHI] You positive
Ishimori's good for you?
Won't be much of a relationship
if she takes off like that
all the time.
I don't expect anything else
from her right now.
Not yet.
[Uka panting]
[UKA]
What's wrong with me?
Why am I like this?
[breathes heavily]
[TOMOYA] I feel like
you should've waited
before going public.
Probably, yeah.
[TOMOYA]
Why didn't you?
Hey.
I was just excited.
[SATORU] Wow, surprised
that even happens to you.
Same here, man.
So, then.
It might be a while still?
[KAI]
That depends on her.
And are you cool with that?
[inhales]
[groans]
[KAI]
Of course not.
[SATORU]
Haven't seen that face before.
[indistinct chatter]
[water trickling]
♪
I've got tomorrow open,
if you've got the time.
[UKA]
What now?
He looked disappointed.
Did I already make him
sick of me?
He said we were in love
this morning.
[KAI] I don't expect anything
else from her right now.
Not yet.
[breathes shakily]
[UKA]
He should expect more.
Hold on, Miura!
Don't give up on me!
[indistinct chatter]
[MALE STUDENT COUNCIL 1]
Kai, you're on duty today.
Here's the script.
STUDENT COUNCIL MEMBERS
[UKA] Mi...
Miura!
-[YURU] Hm?
-Uka?
[TAO]
Uh?
[breathes heavily]
[MALE STUDENT 1] Uh?
So, who's the plain girl?
Keep up, man.
That's Kai's new girlfriend!
[MALE STUDENT 1] Oh.
Didn't know you had one.
♪
That's because we're not
going out yet.
[MALE STUDENT 2] Yeah?
Bummer.
[breathes shakily]
I...
[shudders]
♪
[UKA]
I want to change that.
-Huh?
-So, Miura.
Please, will you
go out with me?
[all gasp]
I'm struggling
to speak my mind.
-I feel nervous...
-[Kai gasps]
...and I doubt that's gonna
change for a while.
But I still wanna try!
[MALE STUDENT COUNCIL 1]
Okay, you're up.
-No. Please don't go.
-[KAI] Uh...
It's okay!
Yeah.
He has to open the assembly.
-Not his choice.
-Yep,
the student council said
today is his day.
My timing is awful as always.
Sorry.
Come on, line up already!
[indistinct chatter]
♪
[UKA]
I can't give up.
Not now...
when it's just beginning.
Rather,
not before it's even begun.
[microphone static]
[FEMALE STUDENT 7]
Kai's opening today?
[FEMALE STUDENT 8]
That's perfect!
-Start the day with some
eye candy! -No kidding.
[KAI]
All right, then.
♪
Welcome.
We're about to
start the morning assembly.
[UKA]
I'll stand strong.
On this...
and everything else!
I will!
Because I want to be with you!
Ishimori.
Would you please
go out with me?
I want you to be my girlfriend.
[breathes shakily]
Anyway,
please refrain from talking.
-That's all.
-Hold up!
-Did he just shoot his shot!
-Don't just leave!
-I can't refrain!
-[gasps]
[female students clamoring]
-[sobbing]
-[MOMO] Aw, Marin. It's okay.
[NAGANO]
Hey, calm down.
[chuckles]
Uka!
[MIZOGUCHI]
Come here. Miura!
That's crazy!
Look at you go, Ishimori!
[Kaede chuckles softly]
[SEKI]
Huh.
[both chuckle softly]
[chuckles]
[BOTH]
Ah!
[SERINA]
You did it.
[indistinct chatter]
[ABE] Okay, okay!
Everyone settle down!
I hope this doesn't bother you
on your first day, Midori.
No.
♪
[Tomoya chuckles softly]
[Uka breathing heavily]
[UKA] I wonder
what's about to begin for us.
[male students laugh]
♪
[chuckles]
[UKA]
I still feel uneasy,
but it's okay.
Something great is starting.
[chuckles softly]
♪
With him!